Asia Dhahir

Front-End developer and UI/UX designer

Details

masif, pirmam erbil, 44001 iraq +964 (783) 114 3663 asia.zahir2000@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Kurd

Skills

Biology

Fast Learner

Ability to Work in a Team

Communication Skills

Time Management

Program Skills

Next Js

React

HTML

Tailwind Css

CSS

JavaScript

Nodejs / Express

MySQL / Mongodb

Github

Terminal

Design Skills

Figma

Wireframing and prototyping skills

Visual communication

Analytical

Adobe XD

Krita

Profile

In spite of I'm Dedicated biological study with more than 4 years of experience at college using modern biology techniques, I'm a passionate front-end develope and UX/UI designer, and creative person who always tries to fill my design works with inventive ideas to connect user problems to design solutions. I have extensive experience developing and supporting user workflows, solid UI/UX design background, strong experience using Figma to create wireframes, mockups, prototypes to communicate, develop, and challenge ideas. I like to code my designs, and enjoy bringing ideas to life in the browser by using react framework and dev tools.

Employment History

Biologist, Volunteer, Pirmam Health Center, Pirmam

APRIL 2021 — JUNE 2021

FrontEnd developer, Part Time, Ovanya Company, Erbil

AUGUST 2021 — PRESENT

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Salahaddin University - College of Science - Biology department, Erbil

AUGUST 2018 — JUNE 2021

Courses

English language course: Elementary, Cambridge College of English

JUNE 2019 — AUGUST 2019

Intermediate - Advanced English, Lagus Online (Udemy)

JULY 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2020

Presentations: Speaking so that people listen, University of California (Coursera)

FEBRUARY 2021 — APRIL 2021

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021, By Colt Steele (Udemy)

AUGUST 2021 — PRESENT

UI/UX Designer Bootcamp 2021, By Rwanga Foundation

OCTOBER 2021— DECEMBER 2021

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/asia-zahir

Behance behance.net/elysiumelys

Github github.com/Asia-Dhahr